question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The movie 'The Nightmare before Christmas' was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Russia passed a law in 2013 which outlaws telling children that homosexuals exist.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'PAYDAY: The Heist' is a sequel to the board game 'Payday'.'",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Waylon Smithers from 'The Simpsons' was originally black when he first appeared in the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Water always boils at 100°C, 212°F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
